Konrad Herbus

Oshawa, ON herbus.konrad@gmail.com (905) 691-5229

Purpose

My first experience when it came to coding occurred in highschool where I was introduced to the basics of web design, javascript, php and mySQL. This was the perfect blend of my interests in graphic design, computers, and learning new languages, which is what initially led me to following the software programming route. By the time I reached the end of my senior year C++ became the primary language being used, providing me with a firm basis in object oriented programming.

University has pushed me to learn a number of new languages through the various projects, and assignments provided each year, whilst also cementing efficient programming techniques and project management skills. Working in Java further expanded on my knowledge in object oriented programming, meanwhile the projects in Python and C highlighted the different advantages and disadvantages each high level language can provide. Most recently, unit testing has been a major focus for software submissions.

Currently I am searching for a workplace opportunity to apply, and expand on the coding knowledge I've gained throughout my educational career. Having worked on both personal, and academic software assignments, the experience of working on professional software projects is something I hope to attain.

Work Experience

Ontario Tech University - *Campus Emergency Response Team*MAY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- Approximately 350 hours on software project
- Regular updates on project progression
- Over 2250 lines of code in variety of languages

Lakeridge Health - Vaccine Administrator

MAY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- Upwards of 3600 vaccines administered
- Patient management during preliminary assessment
- Reassurance by giving accurate information to questions

Student Works - *Sales Associate and Window Cleaner*MAY 2020 - AUGUST 2020

- Both face to face and over the phone sales experience
- Detailing project information and progress to client
- Ensuring quality and timely completion of work

Town of Milton - *Lifeguard and Swim Instructor*SEPTEMBER 2017 - AUGUST 2019

- Preparing lesson plans prior to each week of class
- Report of progress at the end of term for each student
- Proactive incident prevention, along with swift response

Volunteer Experience

Ontario Tech University - Campus Emergency Response Team SEPTEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2021

- Quick response to any campus first aid incidents
- Detailed documentation following any medical call
- Minimum of 12 hours bi-weekly spent on shift

Children's Water Festival - Volunteer Instructor
OCTOBER 2016 & OCTOBER 2018

- Full lessons provided in both English and French
- Students from a variety of schools in the HDSB
- Coordination of various educational games & activities

Operation Wallacea - *Volunteer Research Assistant* MARCH 2018

- Daily wildlife and environmental data collection
- Logging of any research data obtained during excursions
- Lectures on environmental research and climate effects

Town of Milton - Volunteer Swim Instructor

SEPTEMBER 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2017

- Providing individual feedback during each exercise
- Management of student formation to ensure safety
- Roughly 400 hours volunteered as assistant instructor

Education

Ontario Tech University, Oshawa ON Bachelor of Computer Software Engineering SEPTEMBER 2019 - APRIL 2023

 Finishing my third year of software engineering having already obtained efficient project development and management skills

Skills and Certifications

- Programming Languages C, C++, Python, Java
- Web Languages Javascript, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Trilingual (English, Polish, French)
- Emergency Medical Responder BLS
- Aquatic Supervisor LSS